fanprojplay.net 2019-02-17

# Privacy Policy – Fanproj Play

**Fanprojplay.net  **has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, mobile site, application.

#### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, ip or other details to help you with your experience.

#### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**•**  To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

**•**  To improve our website in order to better serve you.

**•**  To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

#### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.  
Cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.fanprojplay.net
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.fanprojplay.net and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites.  **Fanproj Productions  **is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse.

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.fanprojplay.net/contact)

(Visited 1255 times, 4 visits today)
